
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "   Artificial Intelligence is about_____?",
    answer: "Making a machine Intelligent",
    options: [
        "Playing a game on Computer",
        "Making a machine Intelligent",
        "Programming on Machine with your Own Intelligence",
        "Putting your intelligence in Machine",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who is known as the -Father of AI?",
    answer: "John McCarthy",
    options: [
     "Fisher Ada",
     "Alan Turing",
     "John McCarthy",
    "Allen Newell"
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The application/applications of Artificial Intelligence is/are",
    answer: "All of the above ",
    options: [
      "Expert Systems",
      "Gaming",
       "Vision Systems",
      "All of the above "
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Among the given options, which search algorithm requires less memory?",
    answer: "Depth First Search",
    options: [
      "Optimal Search",
      "Depth First Search",
      "Breadth-First Search",
     "Linear Search"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the given language is not commonly used for AI?",
    answer: "Perl",
    options: [
     "LISP ",
"PROLOG",
"Python",
"Perl"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The component of an Expert system is_________.",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Inference Engine",
      "Knowledge Base",
      "User Interface",
      "All of the above"
    ]
},
{
 numb: 7, 
    question: " An AI agent perceives and acts upon the environment using___.",
    answer:   "Both a and c",
    options:[
      "Sensors",
      "Perceiver",
      "Actuators",
      "Both a and c"
    ]
},

{
  numb: 8,
  question: " Among the given options, which is also known as inference rule?",   
  answer:   "Resolution",
  options:[
    "Reform",
"Reference",
"Resolution",
"None of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
    question: " In artificial Intelligence, knowledge can be represented as_______?",
    answer: "Both I and II",
    options:[
      "Predicate Logic",
      " Propositional Logic",
      "Machine Logic",
      "Both I and II"
   
    ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
   question: "Ways to achieve AI in real-life are_________?",
   answer: ". Both a & b",
   options:[
    "Deep Learning",
"Machine Learning",
"Both a & b",
"None of the above"
]

},

];